Don Yoder collection of tape and disc recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Sound recording, 1969 or before, RXH 0786; 1 sound tape reel (01:36:08): analog, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR150)
    Discussion with Mr. Daniel D. Wirt [sic], a member of the Mennonite church, on the background of Amish and Mennonite life. The tape was made by Peter F. Edelman and Alan Solar for Yoder's Religious Theology 523 class. See SR012 for another recording made by them.
    Archivist's note: Rev. Daniel D. Wert died in 1969.
  - Sound recording, February 21, 1960, RXH 0787; 1 sound tape reel (00:59:01): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR151)
    Holy Ghost rally. Recorded at the Met by Ronald Cohen and Kenneth Baer, possibly on behalf of Susan Rosbrow, for Don Yoder's Religious Thought 523 class.
    Gospel songs and remarks by Luther Carroll. Pat Adams, and Louis Casebolt
    Sermon by evangelist Louis Casebolt: "Twentieth Century Fanatics"
  - Sound recording, 1965 or before, RXH 0788; 1 sound tape reel (00:49:08): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR152)
    "Father Divine" as the subject of a paper or talk.
    Recorded by Sidney M. Shenkan and Alan C. Marks, for Don Yoder's Religious Thought 522 [?] class. Reel #2.
    Father Divine died in 1965.
  - Sound recording, undated, RXH 0789; 1 sound tape reel (00:28:53): analog, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR153)
    An Introduction to Jewish Holidays. Recording prepared by Francine Pelly for Don Yoder. Songs performed variously in Hebrew, Yiddish, and English, compiled from various sources, including cantorial and secular traditions. Holidays mentioned include Rosh Hashanah, Purim, and Passover (Pesach).
  - Sound recording, Fall 1971, RXH 0790; 1 sound tape reel (Side A, part 1: 02:01:16, Side A, part 2: 01:57:30, Side B, part 1: 01:59:11, Side B, part 2: 02:00:22): analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR154)
    Don Yoder's folklife studies lectures at the University of Pennsylvania, tape 1 of 2.
    Digitization note: two files were created for each tape side, probably due to the file size limitations at the time they were digitized. The recording for Side B, part 2, begins to speed up around the one-hour mark, suggesting that the recordist changed recording speed during the original capture process. This lasts for about six minutes. The recording begins again about 01:10:18.
  - Sound recording, Fall 1971, RXH 0793; 1 sound tape reel (Side A, part 1: 01:58:36, Side A, part 2: 01:40:22, Side B: 00:44:08): analog, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR155)
    Don Yoder's folklife studies lectures at the University of Pennsylvania, tape 2 of 2.
  - Sound recording, January 31, 1974, RXH 0791; 1 sound tape reel (01:52:34): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR156)
    Lecture on American Indian religion and healing given by John Witthoft to Don Yoder's class at the University of Pennsylvania.
    Notes on the tape box state Witthoft was a professor of anthropology at West Chester University, West Chester, Pennsylvania. In fact, it was his wife Bonita who taught there. Witthoft taught at the University of Pennsylvania from 1966-1986.
  - Sound recording, undated, RXH 0794; 1 sound tape reel (00:15:12): analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR157)
    Interview with G. Gilbert Snyder
    George Gilbert Snyder called himself "Die Wunnerhaus," and had a Pennsylvania German radio show on WEEU, Reading, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording, circa 1970, RXH 0795; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 01:24:36, Side B: 01:07:26): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR158)
    A compilation of recordings of Doukhobors singing, recorded by Mark Mealing, in British Columbia.
    Doukhobors are a Christian religious group of Russian origin. Mark Mealing did his Ph.D. dissertation on Doukhobor hymnody and folklife at the University of Pennsylvania, under Don Yoder's direction. See SR159.
  - Sound recording, circa 1970, RXH 0792; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 00:33:05, Side B: 00:23:54): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR159)
    Doukhobor choral music, recorded by Mark Mealing, until 00:12:22. See notes for SR158. At 00:12:29 Sacred Harp singing begins. This is followed by other forms of Christian song, including African American gospel.
    A compilation of Christian songs from various sources and traditions.
  - Sound recording, 1981 or before, RXF 7462; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 00:08:51, Side B: 00:08:45): analog, mono; 3 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR160)
    Demonstration tape of Ulster dialects, presented by Brendan Adams, dialect archivist at the Ulster Folk Museum (Northern Ireland). Brendan Adams created the tape for Yoder to use in his classes at the University of Pennsylvania.
    Archivist's note: Adams died in 1981.
  - Sound recording, circa 1961, RXH 0796; 1 sound tape reel (00:40:08): analog, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR161)
    Pennsylvania German camp (bush) meeting songs, recorded at the Pennsylvania Dutch Folk Festival, Kutztown, Pennsylvania. Don Yoder is the moderator.
  - Sound recording, undated, RXH 0797; 1 sound tape reel (00:20:12): analog, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR162)
    Pennsylvania German camp (bush) meeting songs, recorded at the Pennsylvania Dutch Folk Festival, Kutztown, Pennsylvania. Don Yoder is the moderator. Performers include Mr. Birkenbusch [spelling unconfirmed], Clarence Kulp, John Moyer, and William Yeakel.
  - Sound recording, circa 1953-1964, RXH 0798; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 01:00:39, Side B: 01:02:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR163)
    A Christian radio program, recorded from a broadcast. On Side A, the program was taped over secular popular music, which still can be heard in the last minute of the recording.
    Notes on the tape box list secular popular music songs.
  - Sound recording, 1970, RXH 0799; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 00:27:56, Side B: 00:08:30): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 3 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR164)
    Examples of Doukhobor hymnody, recorded by Mark Mealing.
    See SR158 and SR159.
  - Sound recording, April 27, 1979, RYN 3008; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:29:39, Side B: 00:30:07): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR165)
    "Symposium on Rural Hymnody," hosted by Berea College, April 27-29, 1979. Recorded at session A, parts 1 and 2. See notes for SR078, Side A.
  - Sound recording, April 27, 1979, RYN 3007; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:11, Side B: 00:29:03): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR166)
    "Symposium on Rural Hymnody," hosted by Berea College, April 27-29, 1979. Recorded at session A, parts 3 and 4. See notes for SR078, Side A.
  - Sound recording, April 27, 1979, RYN 3001; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:09, Side B: 00:30:24): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR167)
    "Symposium on Rural Hymnody," hosted by Berea College, April 27-29, 1979. Recorded at session A, parts 5 and 6. See notes for SR078, Side A.
  - Sound recording, April 28, 1979, RYN 3002; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:14, Side B: 00:29:53): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR168)
    "Symposium on Rural Hymnody," hosted by Berea College, April 27-29, 1979. Recorded at session C, parts 1 and 2. See notes for SR078, Side A.
  - Sound recording, April 28, 1979, RYN 3005; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:44:33, Side B: 00:44:14): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR169)
    "Symposium on Rural Hymnody," hosted by Berea College, April 27-29, 1979. Recorded at session C, parts 3 and 4. See notes for SR078, Side A.
  - Sound recording, April 28, 1979, RYN 3004; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:42:47, Side B: 00:07:09): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR170)
    "Symposium on Rural Hymnody," hosted by Berea College, April 27-29, 1979. Recorded at session C, parts 5 and 6. See notes for SR078, Side A.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYN 3010; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:23:27, Side B: 00:22:13): analog (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR171)
    A compilation of religious and secular songs. Most of the songs on Side 2 seem to be Girl Scout songs sung by girls and women.
  - Sound recording, 1971, RYN 3003; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:31:20, Side B: 00:26:10): analog (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR172)
    Unidentified people discuss the evil eye, luck, and other topics, sometimes unrelated to the collection.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYN 3006; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:37:37, Side B: 00:30:03): analog (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR173)
    Interview of a man born in Russia in 1910. Subjects include discussion of health, the evil eye, Jewish customs, etc. The interview subjects speaks some Yiddish.
    Side B includes the beginning of the interview. Towards the end of Side B there is some talk-back This seems to have been corrected on Side A, which picks up a few seconds after the beginning of the interview. The tape may have been dubbed from a source recording. See notes for SR033.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYN 3009; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:11:52, Side B: 00:36:52): analog (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR174)
    A man recites the Lord's Prayer, then sings "Just a Little Talk with Jesus," "You Gotta Move," "You Can't Hide," "He Didn't Have to Do It, But He Did," and "I Had to Run to the City of Rapture."
    The first song is performed a cappella, and all others accompanied by a drum.
    African American gospel singing, with a man leading a choir. Songs performed include "You Better Run," "One Morning Soon," "There's a Dark Cloud Rising," "The Storm is Passing Over," and several more songs. Unrelated music can be heard faintly at times, which may be print-through from another track.
  - Sound recording, July 13, 1972, RXI 0229; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 01:37:44, Side B: 00:15:00): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR175)
    Interview of Henry Cronister by Don Yoder, in Dubois, Pennsylvania. An unidentified woman's voice can be heard, speaking from the background.
  - Sound recording, May 6, 1973, RXI 0230; 1 sound tape reel (00:45:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR176)
    Zion Reed's Karrich: Deitscher Goddesdinscht
    Pennsylvania Dutch church service. The tape box says Zion Reed's Karrich: Deitscher Goddesdinscht. This may be Zion and St. John's (Reed's) Lutheran Church, in Womelsdorf, Berks County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording, no later than 1951, RXI 0231; 1 sound tape reel (00:45:00): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR177)
    Pennsylvania German songs sung by Mrs. Mary Paul, 90 years old, and Mrs. Valeria Gable, both of Hegins. The recordings were made for Don Yoder's Folklife Studies 550 class.
    Probably a dubbed recording, copied from another source.
  - Sound recording, circa July 13, 1962, RXI 0232; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 00:13:35, Side B: 00:14:17): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR178)
    Selections read from the Bhagavad Gita, in Sanskrit (?) and English.
    About 00:09:07 an unrelated segment begins, featuring Don Yoder, an unidentified woman, and Roger (a young boy) speaking.
    A man sings, with some input from Roger. Also, an unidentified woman speaks. Around 12:05 the woman announces the date as circa July 13, 1962.
  - Sound recording, 1961, RXI 0233; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 00:07:33, Side B: 00:05:33): analog, 7 1/5 ips, half track, mono; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR179)
    "Dial-a-prayer; how Christian Science heals," presented by Barbara Agre Call Rineberg.
    Includes phone recordings of prayers and three people discussing the efficacy of prayer.
  - Sound recording, May 30, 1999, RYQ 3060; 1 sound cassette (00:24:58): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR180)
    Kristine Zakarison (speaker): sermon remembering Grandpa Yoder (Fred R. Yoder; died May 16, 1995). The sermon ends with the announcement of hymn #569, "Touch the Earth Lightly." The recording ends with the introduction to the hymn, played on an organ.
  - Sound recording, undated, RAA 65427; 1 sound tape reel (00:11:05): analog, 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR181)
    A compilation of vocal and instrumental recordings, some possibly dubbed from commercial recordings.
  - Sound recording, November 20, 1971, RXJ 4972; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:24): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR182)
    Jenny C. Trein is interviewed by Don Yoder, and also recites several poems she has written. At the end of the recording, Trein sings a few verses of "Stille Nacht" ("Silent Night") in German. She was a folk artist, well-known for making Moravian "putzes" (three-dimensional representations of Jesus's birth). Recorded in Nazareth, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording, July 15, 1966, RXJ 4973; 1 sound tape reel (00:02:00): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR183)
    Brief recording of Ora Cronister Yoder (Don Yoder's mother), who reads a newspaper inquiry aloud, then says she wrote to Peg Garrison about the Japanese beetles on the raspberry bushes. Recorded in Devon, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording, undated, RXJ 4974; 1 sound tape reel (01:01:00): analog, 1 7/8 ips, full track, mono; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR184)
    Don Yoder and William Woys Weaver interview Mary Thomas about the plain life and related matters. She was an elderly Orthodox Quaker.
  - Sound recording, December 16, 1970, RXJ 4975; 1 sound tape reel (00:31:45): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR185)
    Two interviews regarding the evil eye, told by Rose Volta and Julie Martino to Gregg Chapman. Recorded for Don Yoder's Religious Thought 523 class.
    00:00:07 Interview with Mrs. Rose Volta, a practitioner who can remove the maloik (evil eye).
    00:25:34 Interview with Mrs. Julie Martino Carlin, about having the maloik (evil eye).
  - Sound recording, June 3, 1968, RXJ 4976; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 01:04:16, Side B: 00:59:00): analog, 1 7/8 ips, half track, mono; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR186)
    Archivist's note: the family tree and relationships may not be represented accurately in the interview.
    Digitization notes: Side A has dropout from 00:29:49 to 00:30:20, with some shrill sounds. Recording continues on Side B.
    00:00:24 Don Yoder interviews his uncle Will (William F. Yoder), who describes dampfknudel, a type of steamed or otherwise cooked dumpling. He also spoke about schnitzengnipf (?) (another type of dumpling), apple dumplings, bread-making, the oven used, pie-making, the yeast used, sourdough instead of yeast, rye bread, what he ate for breakfast as a boy, how corn was cooked, how corn mush was eaten, when pie was eaten, shoo-fly pie, ribbelkuche (like a sugar pie), schnitz (apple) pie and other kinds of fruit pie, tzivelkuche (onion pie), kasekuche (something like a custard pie), sauerumble pie (something like rhubarb pie), mince pie, apple butter pie, how and where vinegar is made, how cider is made, making other types of wine, elderberries, sweeteners, butchering and the products, scrapple making, difference between scrapple and pawnhals (?), summer sausage and other types of sausage, time of year for butchering, and who did the work.
    00:30:23 The interviewee talks about his great-grandmother, who lived with her son-in law George Hepler and her daughter Mary Yoder, his grandfather's sister, in Elder Township; the time Grandfather Yoder borrowed money from George Hepler, story about Peter Mowrer (?), story about Father Stein (?), the Suevians, Nelson and Johnny Stein (grandsons of Father Stein), his grandfather William Yoder, whose son Nathan (1841-1914) was the interviewee's father), the badalia (battalia?), the books his grandfather had, a poem his grandmother recited from a magazine, his grandfather's skills as a handyman, his father's educational history, vocations of other relatives, his grandmother Mary Yoder and her family, her husband Jacob Hepler, the school system in those days, practical jokes in school, punishments meted out to students, a visit from one of his mother's school mates, and singing geography.
    Digitization notes: Recording continues from Side A. Shrill sound at the beginning of the recording. The interviewee speaks both in English and Pennsylvania German. The high-pitched tone occurs again at 00:13:10-00:13:15.
    00:00:13 Possibly reading from a history of families in the northeastern part of Higgins Township.
    00:04:13 Story of a Lutheran minister, Daniel Sommer.
    00:05:51 A story about a man who froze to death on the way home.
    00:08:10 The Church's opinion of drinking.
    00:09:14 Story about three men drinking at a barn-raising.
    00:10:36 When a minister said Jesus made grape juice.
    00:11:59 The preacher dealing with an intemperate man.
    00:13:29 Stories about the evangelicals at Higgins: the story about the testimony meeting
    00:14:50 Camp meetings.
    00:17:25 Memories of William Hepler.
    00:17:48 Stories about the Lutherans and the Reformed at Frieden's Church; how they got along.
    00:20:33 Bar room fight over a church matter.
    00:23:08 Story of Sal Groh (?), a girl who was a member of the community having children out of wedlock.
    00:25:03 Story of land owned by Reading Coal and Iron Company, and the improvements it required (a possession house).
    00:26:44 Story about Kessler, an old man who made a comment about the name "Frieden's Kierke."
    00:27:36 Story about Daniel Sommer (?).
    00:28:14 Story about Michael Wolfgang (?), a gunsmith.
    00:29:14 Hermits and eccentric people.
    00:29:47 Tobacco chewing in church.
    00:30:19 Uncle Will's grandmother (Brigitta) was Lutheran; her religious life and activities.
    00:31:17 His grandmother spinning, knitting, dyeing wool..
    00:32:20 The girls spinning; husking bees, Sunday school picnics, camp meetings, etc., and other activities for young people, often leading to marriage.
    00:33:56 Santa Claus; the person who acted as Santa Claus, the costume, etc.; Christmas gifts, Christmas trees, the Pennsylvania Dutch custom of two Christmas Days (the day of and the day after); games on second Christmas Day, shooting on New Year's Day, other New Year's traditions.
    00:38:12 Pinkschte [sic] (Pentacost) not celebrated in Uncle Will's home; Ascension Day, fishing on Ascension Day; St. Patrick's Day was not celebrated, hanging horseshoes.
    00:40:10 Special days for planting, using the almanac,
    00:40:58 Appropriate time for shingling a roof; heavens ruling the earth, unseen spirits.
    00:41:44 Angels, the devil; the fate of a person who died who was not of the faithful.
    00:43:07 The phrase "the devil take you," expressions for cursing, etc.
    00:46:05 The time Uncle Will played Euchre (a card game) in college, and said a curse in Pennsylvania German; when a religious man later rebuked him for using a certain curse.
    00:48:49 Story about an intellectually diminished man who "got religion" and was asked to confess to his sins in public. The public confession of another man.
    00:53:25 When Oliver Kirshner (who was the Lutheran minister at Higgins) wanted to wear a robe when in the pulpit.
    00:54:43 Story about a family who lived in one of the "possession houses."
    00:56:12 Story about a boy he knew when he was at Westchester Normal School, who was one of the "plain clothes" people, regarding baptism.
    00:56:51 Story about how the Reformed Mennonites got started.
  - Sound recording, November 9, 1966, RXJ 4977; 1 sound tape reel (00:06:46): analog; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR187)
    Recorded by (?) Zenzinger.
    00:00:04 A woman sings in Pennsylvania German, with piano accompaniment, before an audience. The beginning of the song is cut off.
    00:02:05 The woman speaks with a man, in Pennsylvania German.
    00:02:21 A woman sings another song in Pennsylvania German, with piano accompaniment.
    00:04:27 A man (a moderator, possibly Don Yoder) speaks in English, and invites questions from the audience. One man asks a question, and the singer responds. The moderator names a book that will be for sale.
  - Sound recording, undated, RXJ 4978; 1 sound tape reel (00:15:15): analog; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR188)
    Milton Kuhns speaks in Pennsylvania German (possibly reading from a text), and also sings songs in Pennsylvania German, with piano accompaniment.
  - Sound recording, May 12, 1978, RXJ 4979; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 01:35:22, Side B: 00:06:30): analog; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR189)
    The date is announced on Side B, and may be the same date for Side A.
    Don Yoder provides guidance for William Woys Weaver, who interviews H. Carl Weaver speaking about barn-building, especially particular dialect words, as he is make a dictionary. Weaver also talks about other farm-related topics, school, etc. Yoder also participates in the interview process. Recording made at H. Carl Weaver's house, RD 1, Strasburg, Pennsylvania.
    William Weaver interviews Mary Larkin Thomas at her home in Westchester, Pennsylvania, on various topics.
  - Sound recording, undated, RXJ 4980; 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 00:02:39, Side B: 00:02:39): analog; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR190)
    On both tape sides, an unidentified man delivers a sermon (?) in Pennsylvania German, with some English. Both tape sides end abruptly.
  - Sound recording, January 20, 1978, RXJ 4981; 1 sound tape reel (00:16:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR191)
    Rev. Howard Finster talks about his paintings at the American Folklife Center; "with religious song and harmonica tune." This is a copy of a tape in the Howard Finster collection (AFC 1984/016).
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3062; 1 sound cassette (00:05:57): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR192)
    A small group of men and women sing religious songs in Pennsylvania German.
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #1.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3063; 1 sound cassette (00:15:21): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR193)
    Bush meeting songs, sung in harmony by John Moyer and William Yeakel. John Moyer speaks in English on preaching, revival meetings, and related topics. Don Yoder interviews him. This tape may be dubbed from one or more other tapes.
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #2.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3064; 1 sound cassette (00:27:39): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR194)
    Don Yoder presents the story of Susanna Cox and the ballad tradition, and introduces Carrie Bonser Weaver, who sings "Susannah Cox" at an outdoor event. See SR113 and SR118 for similar recordings.
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #3.
  - Sound recording, 1961, RYQ 3065; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:09, Side B: 00:14:43): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR195)
    Recorded at the Pennsylvania Dutch Folk Festival, Kutztown, Pennsylvania.
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #4.
    Don Yoder introduces a program on hymnody in the Lutheran and Reformed churches, the plain Dutch tradition, and Pennsylvania Dutch tradition of the revivalist groups. This may be a copy of a recording from the "Symposium on Rural Hymnody."
    The program begins abruptly. A minister leads a group in singing Pennsylvania German religious songs. This may be a recording from the Kutztown Festival, and is probably dubbed from various tapes. The balance of the recording is similar to or the same as SR114.